(Sheldon:)Of course, but not by myself.
Really? Never?
Well, once, when I was 15
and spending the summer...
(Sheldon:)...at the Heidelberg Institute in Germany.
- Studying abroad?
- No, visiting professor.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, the local cuisine was a little more
sausage-based than I'm used to...
(Sheldon:)...and the result
was an internal blitzkrieg...
(Sheldon:)...with my lower intestine
playing the part of Czechoslovakia.
And there was no one there
to take care of you?
No, my mom had to fly back to Texas
to help my dad...
(Sheldon:)...because the house had slipped off
the cinder blocks again.
(Leonard:)- Again?
- It was tornado season.
And it was an aluminum house.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, the housekeeper in the faculty
residence didn't speak any English.
(Sheldon:)When I finally managed
to convince her I was sick...
(Sheldon:)...she said,
"Möchtest du eine Darmspülung?"
(Penny:)What does that mean?
(Sheldon:)Based on what happened next, I assume
it means, "Would you like an enema?"